<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Research Hero</string>
    <string name="research_topic_lesson">
        First, you must identify a field of study that you would like to research.
        \n\n
        At the student level, you will either be assigned a topic during a course or choose a
        lab that performs research that interests you.
        \n\n
        -	Choose a subject that excites you or that you find yourself drawn to.
        \n\n
        -	Scientific research isn’t limited to just subjects like biology, chemistry, and physics. As long as you follow the scientific method to perform your study you are doing research.

    </string>
    <string name="research_topic_quiz">
        Question: \nScientific research is Only limited to just subjects
        like biology, chemistry, and physics.
    </string>
    <string name="research_purpose_lesson">
        The research purpose is a statement of "why" the study is being conducted,
        or the goal of the study. The goal of a study might be to identify or describe
        a concept or to explain or predict a situation or solution to a situation that
        indicates the type of study to be conducted.
        \n\n
        The purpose statement identifies the variables, population and setting for a study.
        Every study has an explicit or implicit purpose statement.
        \n\n
        The research purpose should be stated objectively or in a way that does not reflect
        particular biases or values of the researcher.
        \n\n
        In the research process, the purpose is usually stated after the problem,
        supports the problem and clarifies the knowledge to be generated for nursing.
    </string>
    <string name="research_purpose_quiz">
        Question: \n
        In the research process, the purpose is usually stated after the problem.
    </string>
    <string name="research_question_lesson">
        The research question will be the main focus of your study. 
        Once you have a chosen a topic that interests you, investigate some of the
        unanswered questions within that field. The research question should be based in
        a field that you have some familiarity with. You can have more than one research
        question for a scientific study.
        \n\n
        -	Do a brief literature search to familiarize yourself with what
        information is already out there and what unanswered questions there are.
        \n\n
        -	Make sure you have the necessary resources available to 
        you (funding and laboratory equipment) to work on the question.
        \n\n
        -	Talk to professors or other researchers and have them help you identify
        a question that you could work on.
        \n\n
        -	Many articles will state some of the unanswered questions and
        speculate on future directions or suggest experiments that will be
        necessary in the future. Use these as a springboard for your own ideas.
    </string>
    <string name="research_question_quiz">
        Question: \n
        Don\'t ever Talk to professors or other researchers for them
        to help you identify a question that you could work on.
    </string>
    <string name="hypothesis_lesson">
        The researcher generates intermediate hypotheses to describe a solution to the problem.
        \n\n
        This is at best a temporary solution since there is as yet no evidence 
        to support either the acceptance or rejection of these hypotheses.
    </string>
    <string name="hypothesis_quiz">
        Hypothesis is a temporary solution.
    </string>
    <string name="experiment_lesson">
        1.	Determine the sample size. In order for your experiment to be meaningful,
        you need to have an experimental sample size large enough to perform statistical
        analyses on. In order to determine this, you need to know some information about
        your experimental population and use a power analysis calculator.
        \n\n
        -	To use a power analysis, you need to have an estimate of the effect size,
        an estimation of the variability within the data (standard deviation), the level
        of significance (standard convention is p=0.05), and power (the rate of false
        negatives you are willing to accept, generally set at 80%).
        \n\n
        -	Running smaller pilot studies can help you gather the necessary information
        for a proper power analysis to calculate sample size.
        \n\n
        -	 If you don’t have the means to do a pilot study, use some rough estimations
        based on information you have gathered from the literature.
        \n\n
        2.	Identify all of the necessary solutions and equipment. When designing the experiment,
        you need to know all of the solutions you will need to use and the type of equipment
        you will need access to. Many universities have core facilities with instruments
        you can use if your specific lab does not have all of the equipment necessary. 
        \n\n
        -	You may need to be trained on the equipment and develop the proper expertise
        before you can start your experiments. Keep this in mind when planning a timeline.
        \n\n
        -	If you don’t have access to the necessary equipment, you might consider working
        with collaborators who have the equipment and expertise.
        \n\n
        3.	State all experimental conditions. The key to a well-designed experiment is to
        have a manageable number of testable conditions.[10] If you are doing a drug study,
        you probably want to test different dosages, but you don’t want too many. You will
        likely have to do a few smaller experiments to optimize the test conditions you will
        use in the final experiments. 
        \n\n
        -	Literature searches can help you identify time points, dosages, and 
        treatment conditions relevant to your studies.
        \n\n
        4.	Include the necessary controls. Experimental data is useless without the proper
        control conditions to compare them to. A control is a condition that is kept constant
        and used to measure the change of the experimental condition.
        \n\n
        -	A proper experiment has only one variable and multiple controls to ensure
        that any changes seen in the results are due specifically to the variable
        that was changed.
        \n\n
        -	To test different variables, you will need to perform multiple experiments.
        \n\n
        5.	Define the experimental outcomes. In research you must identify and define
        what the outcome is for your study.[12] You also want to define what you consider
        “success” of an experiment. If you are studying a biological process, the outcome
        may be the measure of the amount of a specific protein produced. 
        \n\n
        -	The outcomes must be measurable with consistency or they will not produce usable data.
        \n\n
        -	All statistical analyses to be used for the study should be established 
        before data collection.
        \n\n
        6.	Write up the experimental protocol. After completing the overall design
        of the experiment, write up a detailed protocol that includes every condition
        to be tested and all the necessary calculations. Performing the experiment is
        much simpler when you have done all of planning before you begin. 
        \n\n
        -	The more detailed you make the protocol, the easier it will be to follow 
        and repeat the experiment later.

    </string>
    <string name="experiment_quiz">
        To test different variables, you don\'t need to perform any experiments.
    </string>
    <string name="analysis_lesson">
        Analyze the raw data. For most experiments, you will be given a raw data
        output of numbers. Depending on the study, you will transfer these numbers
        into another program to make graphs and compare the various groups. 
        \n\n
        It’s important to pay close attention to the data when moving it between programs. 
        \n\n
        -	Take care to avoid copying and pasting rows or columns of data incorrectly.
    </string>
    <string name="analysis_quiz">
        To avoid copying and pasting rows or columns of data incorrectly, pay no attention.
    </string>
    <string name="radio_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="radio_no">No</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
