<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Research Hero</string>
    <string name="research_topic_lesson">
        First, you must identify a field of study that you would like to research.
        \n\n
        At the student level, you will either be assigned a topic during a course or choose a
        lab that performs research that interests you.
        \n\n
        -	Choose a subject that excites you or that you find yourself drawn to.
        \n\n
        -	Scientific research isn’t limited to just subjects like biology, chemistry, and physics. As long as you follow the scientific method to perform your study you are doing research.

    </string>
    <string name="research_topic_quiz">
        Question: \nScientific research is Only limited to just subjects
        like biology, chemistry, and physics.
    </string>
    <string name="research_purpose_lesson">
        The research purpose is a statement of "why" the study is being conducted,
        or the goal of the study. The goal of a study might be to identify or describe
        a concept or to explain or predict a situation or solution to a situation that
        indicates the type of study to be conducted.
        \n\n
        The purpose statement identifies the variables, population and setting for a study.
        Every study has an explicit or implicit purpose statement.
        \n\n
        The research purpose should be stated objectively or in a way that does not reflect
        particular biases or values of the researcher.
        \n\n
        In the research process, the purpose is usually stated after the problem,
        supports the problem and clarifies the knowledge to be generated for nursing.
    </string>
    <string name="research_purpose_quiz">
        Question: \n
        In the research process, the purpose is usually stated after the problem.
    </string>
    <string name="radio_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="radio_no">No</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
